Thank you for watching!
Thanks for all your hard work.
Everyone eat together?
Hallo! This time with Maria Makino from Morning Musume 23 and Ayano Kawamura from Angerme.
I will be presenting this time with these two, so please bear with me until the end.
It was announced late last month that Morning Musume and Angerme have new members.
Morning Musume When they met for the first time, the Morning Musume members asked questions one by one,
They were so cute that I fell in love with them.
I have not met her yet, so I would like to meet her and ask her to show us her special skills so that I can fall in love with her, too.
Yukiho and Hana Goto joined Angerme from among the Halopro trainees on the lower board.
When Mr. Takeuchi announced that they would be joining Angerme, I was very moved,
I was very moved, but before that, there were many things I wanted to talk about,
I thought she was really talkative, energetic, and cheerful.
I saw her perform in the performance test and as a trainee,
I saw both of them perform in the performance.
They had an aura when they were performing,
I thought it was really cool,
I'm really looking forward to performing Angstrom's songs with them.
I can already imagine how cool they are.
Haruka Inoue and Ayako Yumokeda will make their debut on June 26 at the Nippon Budokan.
Yukiho Shimoita and Hana Goto will be unveiled on June 11 at the Nakano Sanparaza.
Please look forward to it.
Please take a look at this video first.
Please enjoy!
Thank you for watching.
Say I love you.
I have to say it out loud.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
I still love you lady
Do it Do it Do it
I'm gonna have so much fun
Don't dwell on one love
The love you love, it'll never stop
I read the sadness of others behind the sadness of others
I'll never be free to do anything I want
Geraci, let's keep going.
Possessiveness is one of love
Sad choice, the chance of love
Everybody clap your hands Everybody clap your hands
Everybody clap your hands Everybody
Everybody clap your hands Everybody clap your hands Everybody clap your hands
The one who makes the best use of his time wins
It's starting, romance's on the way
Everybody clap your hands Everybody clap your hands
Oh, it's gonna be an end rain
Let's dance in our dreams
The future's in your hands, it's changing
A little bit more time
We'll get through it
Say I love you.
I want to say it out loud and clear
Oh, my God, I still love you Yeah
The whole town loves you
Do it Do it
It's a romance in the middle of a romance
♪ Don't you love someone you don't even know?
Everybody starts out rather old
You're supposed to be taller than your years
You don't want to talk about the old days, do you?
When you get to the phone without "All of you
I bet there's at least a laugh
A message of love, of dreams.
Sometimes it's nice to have a night like that
Everybody got a heart Everybody knows
It's starting, romance is on the way
Let's follow the romance forever
Oh, and so we dance in a zero-gravity, tsunami
Sometimes we see each other like we can't stop
♪ Happenings are waiting for you beyond this night
Say I love you
I have to say it out loud and clear
I still love you again
Bachoo, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
Full way to way It's starting
Romance is in the air
I'll go to the matteau
Black Hevia
Say I love you.
I still love you
I still love you Do it Do it
Do it, do it, do it
I still love you
It's starting, the middle of romance
Thank you for everything. I'm rooting for you, too.
Morning Musume 23 Maria Makino and Ayano Kawamura of Angerme present "Halo! STE.
From here, I'd like to talk a little about each other.
I'm going to ask you a few questions, so please answer them quickly and without thinking too much.
Okay, I'll get right to it.
Then let's get started.
This Halo! Sta. will be distributed on June 7!
S/mileage Amano shaku was released in 2009
What is the first thing that comes to mind when you hear this song?
Your bicycle has changed.Your bike has changed.
New single 2 round 6 love beast to be released next week on June 14.
What is the best part of the dance for this song?
The choreography during the interlude when everyone turns their backs!
It was so cool!
Alumni of the new single
What was your honest impression when you received the song?
It has a Kansai dialect.
Please tell us a secret story about Ayuno Kawamura that hasn't been told to the public.
I have 45,000 photos in my folder.
Forty-five thousand pictures.
That's amazing!
Hello! Project celebrates its 25th anniversary this year.
What song would you choose as the background music when breaking up tuna?
Hachano-uma's festival debut!
That's all. I think you might want to get to know Ayano Kawamura a little better,
There are a lot of things I'm curious about. The dance of "Beast of Love" is really cool, and I got to see it on music video,
Thank you very much.
It was very powerful, just like The Angelmo.
The choreography of cutting the back was done by everyone, so I was able to see everyone from an angle I have never seen before,
It was very fresh.
That's an interesting impression.
Then there was the background music when they were dismantling the tuna.
I knew the festival debut would have a festive feel to it.
There are calls of "Sole, Sole, Sole, Sole, Sole, Sole, Sole, Sole, Sole, Sole, Sole, Sole, Sole, Sole, Sole,
I think it fits perfectly with the atmosphere of the demolition show.
I see. Thank you very much. It was a lot of fun.
Questions for Makino-san will come after the VTR.
Hallo! Ste.
Angerme, Ai no Kedamono, June 14, onser.
Angerme Escape Life June 14 onser.
Angerme I wanted to love you, I couldn't love you, I won't kiss you okay
Angerme, I couldn't even tell you, Ai no Kedamono, June 14, Onsur yo
The Budokan concert has ended.
Thank you very much.
It was our 10th anniversary, so I was very happy to spend time with you all at the live,
I am also very happy to be able to hear your voices on such a big stage,
Now, don't make eye contact with Katakna.
Akaringo!
Well, I was crying just now because I was so happy and joyful,
The reason why I cried was because I wasn't crying during my own MC,
But when I heard Kudo-san's MC,
I was crying because I was having fun and was happy.
It made me cry.
Really?
I cried again.
That was fun, too.
I think it was a very, very memorable show.
The big environment was completed...
The big environment was completed,
Great impression!
It was a great impression.
Hokkaido, Hokkaido, Osaka, Osaka, so I would like to do my best to see you again.
Let's do our best.
And, a new member, Mifchan Kawashima, has joined the group,
How was it for you, Mifchan?
Did you think it was a big stage?
Today, I met all the members,
I met all the members and performed in a Japanese dance performance for the first time,
I felt that I finally became a member of Juice-Juice,
From the moment I said "I am Mifu Kawashima of Juice-Juice", everyone welcomed me with warmth,
I was really happy that everyone welcomed me so warmly when I told them I was Mifu Kawashima of Juice-Juice,
I hope to do my best again so that I can perform with you all soon.
I am looking forward to it!
I'm looking forward to working hard with you all,
I want to work hard with you, and I want to make Juice-Juice a big success,
I would like to continue to run through our 10th anniversary year,
Thank you for your support.
That's all for Juice-Juice.
Halo! Stay!
Next, I would like to ask a question to Ms. Makino.
I'll enjoy it.
Your photo book "Dear Maria!" was released on June 10.
What kind of Makino-san do you think this book is full of?
Let's see, mature?
Wanko, wanko, wanko is taking pictures.
How did you condition yourself for the book?
This is the period of facial beauty.
Makino-san's favorite professional baseball team is in the middle of an interleague game.
Who is the member of Hello! Project that you would like to communicate with?
Ayano Kawamura.
I'm going down.
What do you like to accompany yourself to baseball games?
Fried red ginger. It's sold at Marin.
What song would you choose as the 4th ace in the Hello!
Uh, "Love Machine".
Oh, wow.
Yes, Love Machine. It's going on sale. A photo book.
There was a dog in the studio, so I was holding him the whole time,
I think that the cut is used in the book, so it's really cute.
It's a very cute shot of Makino-san and the dog. Wow, I'm looking forward to it.
Let's see, the Hello! Project member you would like to communicate with now is me,
That's right.
I'm so glad.
I've been wanting to invite Ayano Kawamura for lunch for about 4 days now,
But I was a little worried because I thought it was too sudden.
I also told the manager yesterday.
I would like to have lunch with Ms. Makino, can I ask her out?
Is that so?
Yes, that's right.
So let's go!So let's go!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's definitely go!
I'm so happy.
Hallo! Ste.
Hello! Please subscribe to the Steecoach channel.
I am Masashi Natsuyaki.
This is Yumeno Kishimoto from Tsubacaktory.
I will do my best today.
Now, teacher, what would you like to make today?
Yes, today, it's face Mangai.
Oh, wow, this is Yumeno's one.
This is Yumeno's request, isn't it?
That's right.
I have a hunch.
Yes, yes, that image.
It can be cooked quickly.
So, where would you like to start this time?
The toppings, or rather, the decorations.
When I said "face Mangai," I knew it was lettuce sliced and slanted.
Cucumbers.
Cucumber on top of cucumber.
What did you say?
I said lettuce.
I also thought lettuce could be a pattern.
Why did lettuce come up?
I just thought I'd ask now.
I thought it was cucumber.
I would like you to slice the cucumber again.
I'd like it if you could put it in a larger size because of the sauce and the seasoning.
Yes, that would be great.
Open this one and do it like this normally.
Is this okay?
Yes, that's right.
The lemon is two thirds of a lemon.
I wanted to cut the edge of the lemon a little cooler.
I wanted to cut the edges in a cool way.
Wow, that looks difficult.
It's right in the middle.
That's how you cut it.
You sometimes see that with eggs, don't you?
Yes, it does happen.
If you are too scared and only put a little bit in, you can't cut it.
It's not quite right.
Then, do your best.
Yes, I did.
It's done.
I noticed that it was really big.
Don't worry, it'll be fine.
I guess we can't reach the goal yet.
That's not that either, is it?
It's okay.
Is it okay?
Just hang in there.
You can only do it once.
Here we go.
Ah! It's done. It's done. That's great!
You can do it. It's okay, it's okay.
It's done.
Oh, I didn't know we were going to cut it like this.
Now it's time to make the sauce.
First, 1 tablespoon of soy sauce.
1 tablespoon of Nampula.
1 tablespoon vinegar.
Less than a teaspoon of sugar.
Great, I knew I could smell it.
Did it dissolve?
Yes, I think so.
Then leave it.
And here is the most important part.
Ginger and garlic.
Ginger again, just like before, it's a great deal.
Yes, it is.
I already knew that.
Now we're going to mince it very finely.
Very fine.
I have prepared a technique.
To make it fine,
I think you see the way they do the chopping,
You may remember it today.
Let's support it and hold it down.
Let's support it and try a little.
Yes, this is the cut.
That's just about right.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
You're really good at it, aren't you?
No, no, no, really.
It's very easy to get involved in the sauce.
If only they were this small.
It's good, isn't it?
It's good. It looks easy to eat.
In a bowl.
Put them in a bowl.
And put the garlic in the same way.
Yes.
I feel like I'm getting the hang of it.
And it's even better. You are doing it like an expert.
Really? I did it.
You can cut the leeks like this and then cut them into small pieces like this,
But leeks tend to be cut like this,
But since leeks tend to go poofy like this, you can cut them in half diagonally, and when all the leeks are cut, turn them the other way and do the same.When all the pieces are done, turn it the other way and do the same thing.
Oh, no, I'm going to cut it. It's okay.
Oh, no, I'll cut it off. Oh, no, I'm going to cut it.
The green onions are floating inside, so I start from here like this.
You are not mad at me, right, sir? I'm not mad at all.
I thought he had a bad beard and wondered if he was OK.
Was it like that? Oh, this? This way?
No, it's not like that. It's like this. From the top.
Yes, yes, yes. This way, it would be a little crushed.
I see. While letting air in. Cutting while letting air in.
What do you think? This is a good way to wash it.
Is it okay? It's fine.
You used a quarter of the leeks.
Next. Put 2 tablespoons of sesame oil in the pan.
Please. 2 tablespoons.
Then turn on the heat. Do you want it on high heat?
No, let's use medium heat. Medium heat.
Here's a near miss point. Sesame oil should be hot.
Very hot.
But if you let it get to the point where it starts to smoke, the aroma of the sesame oil will be too strong.
It's difficult, isn't it? That's right.
It's coming already. Is it coming already?
It's already here. The timing is right.
Yes, stop it. I'll stop.
Okay, here. This way?
Over here? Put it down, put it down.
Come on in, come on in. Put it all in.
Is that what you're doing?
What do you think? It smells so good.
I'm going to get in there where it's hot. Great.
I'll put the sauce in too.
You can taste it.
Wow, it looks delicious!
Great reaction!
This is good for rice!
Great!
Yes, then everyone's favorite chili sauce!
Here comes the second sauce!
This one is pretty thick, so you can just pour it over the rice.
This is 1 part water to 1 part fish sauce.
Strictly speaking, I think the cc's and grams are a little different.
I think 50 is fine.
Add a little bit of fish sauce.
A little bit of fish sauce, what does that really mean?
I don't think it's too little if you like it.
Or a little more if you want it a little stronger.
Okay, so mix it once, and it's not good to taste it, so...
Here we go!
Yes, it's good!
Are you okay?
Hot, hot!
That's good, that's good, that's good.
Okay, this consistency is fine.
Okay, let's go.
Sauce is OK, too.
By the way, if you don't like fish sauce, you can substitute soy sauce.
Now that the rice is ready, let's take a look.
Hello!
Looks delicious!
This is absolutely delicious!
I'll save the green onions too.
I don't use leeks.
You can use them if you want.
Let's eat it on a separate plate.
It might be hard to cut if the skin is on top.
It is better to make it high.
If you cut it too small
Maybe you can cut it into quarters.
Is it dry and flaky?
It's not soggy at all.
Here it is.
Don't wash.
By the root of frying without washing.
Looks delicious!
Here we go
Good morning.
Looks good
If you keep the bottom of the pan
It's stable.
Put it over the top.
Cute.
It's pretty
Brilliant.
I think it's ready, don't you?
It's nice.
Kawangaii is complete.
Yay!
Ta-da!
The face cartoon shop is complete!
I'm so happy!
How do you like it, Yume?
Well, it's a store now.
It's a store!
The quality is so high that I can't believe you made it.
Yes, it is.
It looks delicious!
Well, you should try it now.
Are you sure? Bon appétit.
Here you go.
Is it good?
Juicy!Juicy!
Delicious!
Good!
The rice is battery too!
Excellent!
I had a high Hello Kitchen hurdle in my mind,
I thought I can't cook in front of people,
But under the two of you.
I was just watching,
I was just watching, and the teacher and I worked together to get to this point.
It was the first time for me to enjoy cutting vegetables with a knife.
Really?
So, when you are going to cook at home, what do you think?
I think it lowered my hurdle for cooking in a good way.
That's great!
I hope you will make it again at home,
I hope you can make use of it in the future.
Thank you very much, Yume-chan-sensei.
Thank you very much.
That's all for Hello Kitchen.
Good bye!
Well, it looked delicious, but Ena Kawamura, you handle fish, don't you?
Is there any other cooking you can do? Well, I can cook, but after I cut the fish, I make this sashimi and use the leftover bones to make arajiru, or something like that.
I also like to make arajiru with the leftover bones from the sashimi.
I like to take the fillet part of the tuna when it's dismembered, and roast it in the oven and eat it.
I'd love for you to try it.
I want to eat it every day, so I wanted her to be next to me.
Do you have any specialties? I don't cook at all, but I can make o-hagi.
You can make o-hagi? That's a serious thing, starting with rice planting.
That's how I learned how to make them. If you make ohagi again, I'd love to eat them, so please bring some.
Halo! I'll make it again sometime.
Morning Musume 23 Maria Makino and
23 Maria Makino of Morning Musume '23 and Ayano Kawamura of Angerme's Presenting Halo! STE
Project 2023 Spring City Circuit will be held in Osaka.
Project 2023 Spring City Circuit will be held in Osaka, and the Summer City Circuit will be held in Yokohama Arena on June 21.
Project 2023 Spring City Circuit will be held in Osaka, and the Summer City Circuit will be held on June 21 at Yokohama Arena.
Akari Takeuchi Final Live Angerme Yori Ai wo Makimetto (With Love from Angerme) will be held at Nippon Budokan on June 26th.
Morning Musume' at Nippon Budokan on June 26th. 23 25th Anniversary Concert Tour
Glad Quarter Century at Nippon Budokan will be held!
So I've summarized the highlights of this show in a few words, and I'd like to introduce them to you!
Here we go!
Ta-da!
I, Kawamura, have chosen "Big Love" as the highlight of this show.
I know that the title of the show is "Big Love",
but also because it was Akari Takeuchi's graduation concert,
I also wanted to express my big love for Ms. Takeuchi,
I also wanted to express my big love to all the fans,
I hope the concert will be filled with big love.
She is so cute.
I wrote Morning Musume s concert 25th anniversary.
The highlight of the show is as it is,
Now that Morning Musume is celebrating its 25th anniversary,
I hope you will come to see the concert,
I hope you will come and see the concert.
Please come to Yokohama Arena on June 21 and Nippon Budokan on June 26.
Next, let's meet DJ Akaringo!
Princess
I'm ready to go
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Make it, Make it, Feel it. Party okay
I'm ready to go, make it, make it, feel it
Here comes the explosion
Too much heaven, too much feathers
I don't know how to live
It's easy to see, confidence is so
The depths of my body
I've got the center sauna on my back
This is good, this is mine
Abaretekka Habagbudai
Abaretekka Habagbaddi
I'm cool, I'm cool, I'm cool, I'm cool, I'm cool, I'm cool, I'm cool, I'm cool
Gotta get it, got it, got it, got it, got it, got it, got it, got it.
We're gonna do everything we want to do.
Gotta go, gotta go, gotta go, gotta go, we're going down.
Oh, come on, it's your style. It's dangerous streets.
It's a complicated time, so let's go wild!
I'm gonna go wild!
Ah, I wanna take a have a good time
To the feelings
I wanna take a have a good time
Oh, shoot me through here
Abaretekker! Avaratekker! Avaratekker!
Yeah! Yikes! Ikepanda!
MATCHER! Yeah! Bing bong!
I've developed a one-word vocabulary.
I'm in love. I'm in love because I'm scared.
I'm sure that's him.
He's lonely, he's loud, he's lonely.
I don't need that anymore!
Avaretekker! Goodbye!
He says he's in pain.
Avarattekker! Okay! Let me go!
Let me go, go, go! You know you like it, don't you?
Rock 'n' punk, Bourdokan's the best
I'm a babe, I'm a babe, I'm a babe, I'm a babe.
We're not getting any better.
Let's do everything we want to do
Gah, gah, gah, gah, gah, gah, gah, gah, gah, gah, gah, gah, and sinkGah, gah, gah, gah, gah, gah, gah, gah, gah, gah, and then it sinks.
I don't know. It's not mechanical anymore.
Guincy, you can't win. It's our time.
Heroes don't even pass through the streets anymore.
Let me go.
Thank you.
By H.
We are the chosen ones The beasts to blame
Whatever happens, we will not be defeated.
We will not mix up the truth of what we are and the truth of what we are chasing.
We don't mix up our consciousness and the truth we're chasing
I'm not interested in being a fad.
We're all different, each and every one of us.
I've never been here before, but it's obvious.
It's not just the hair on the side. It's this feeling.
I've never been here before, but I feel nostalgic.
It's not like I've seen it in a dream or something. It's just this feeling.
I don't have to explain it to you.
I know.
Ambitions to be fulfilled Collections to be discarded
I prepare, I let out, and the minute I let out, the sound comes back.
The future we're supposed to meet is a badly made truth
That's the whole story.
I don't care about the gossip.
If I have time for gossip, I'll run.
Next time I see you, we'll skip the introduction.
Let's start from the beginning. Let's have fun. Let's be extravagant.
Next time we see each other, we don't have to say goodbye.
It'll be like we've known each other longer than we've known each other since childhood.
I don't have to explain anything to you.
You know what I mean.
It's the first time I've ever heard you say it, but it feels right.
It's not just a feeling of destiny. It's a feeling.
I've never heard it before, but it feels familiar.
It's not just a feeling I had in a dream or something. It's a feeling.
I don't have to explain it to you.
Yeah, I know.
Subtitle: Kiminomiya
Thank you for everything. I'm rooting for you too.
Morning Musume 23Maria Makino and Aino Kawamura of Angerme are presenting Halo! Ste.
It's time to say goodbye.
Here is an announcement.
Starting tomorrow, June 8, each group will perform at the Farewell Nakano Sunplaza Music Festival.
Morning Musume 23Angelum will both perform on the 11th.
We would like to perform with our gratitude.
And Morning Musume 23 will have an additional performance of their spring tour on June 10 at NHK Osaka Hall.
I will do my best on the last day of the spring tour.
Also, Maria Makino's photo book "Dear Maria" will be released on June 10.
Please take a look at the 9th photo book.
Angerme's new single "Ai no Kedamono Dousou" will be released next week on June 14.
The music video is now available on YouTube, so I hope you will watch and listen to it.
Angerme Single V "I gotta go! will be released on July 12.
And Morning Musume 23 and Angerme Juice- Juice will perform at Rockin' Japan Festival 2023.
Let's get excited this summer too.
The Hallo! Project members will appear more and more on this channel.
Project members. New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel.
This time, we'll be talking with Maria Makino, a member of Morning Musume 23 Maria Makino and Ayano Kawamura from Angerme,
23 and Ayano Kawamura of Angerme.
Farewell!